Last time on Zombieland Saga Revenge, we were still bummed about the show we bombed.
All we could do was work our part-time jobs and wait for our manager to get a haircut
and pull it together, but he wouldn't come out of his bunk!
He did show up at our comeback performance at Guile's, only to get his butt kicked, but
either way, he still inspired us to keep moving forward.
Now it's time for our revenge to begin for real!
We may just be seven girls who died in Saga, but we got a second chance and we're not gonna
waste it!
Even if they say it can't be done, we'll sing and dance our way to the top!
Because we're Fun Shushu!
Sakura, is everything okay?
Yeah.
I was just thinking about how we're gonna be active as idols in the future.
It made me kinda nervous.
Hey, that's okay.
Comfort's important, but it isn't good to be too relaxed either.
Uh, what are you doing, Saki?
Well, you do need a lot of power to sing and dance, don't ya?
And we're trying to take over the whole country.
I'm not sure that exercise matters for zombies, though.
Sure it does!
Saga and Ship Z worked, didn't it?
I'mma be ripped in no time flat!
Okay.
Go!
Saki has a real talent for getting people to follow her lead.
Yeah, something about her passion is infectious.
Grieved and
Hesus, Hahahaha...
It takes than me!
Hanajajajaja
NotAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAll section
You are a really amazing and holy увер member paid to allow you.
Phey off Kanye zuраст,
upset, LAKE,